<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Coast Business Technologies</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Coast Business Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</webMaster>
    <copyright>(c) 2018 Boyd Kelly</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/2014/09/28/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2014/09/28/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>/2014/03/10/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2014/03/10/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jula Alphabet</title>
      <link>/2018/07/30/alpha-jula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 22:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2018/07/30/alpha-jula/</guid>
      <description>    Comme en français Exemple Jula Sens français     a papa saga mouton   aa pâte baara travail   an blanc sanji pluie   b bol baga bouillie   c match cɛ homme   d dos disi poitrine   e école bese machète   ee féerie feere vendre   en  sen pied   ɛ mère sɛnɛ agriculture   ɛɛ  mɛɛn durer   ɛn  bɛn entente   f fer foro champ   g gant mɔgɔ personne   gw  gwa foyer   h hello (anglais) hakili intelligence   i Iit misi boeuf   ii  miiri pensée   in I Min boire   j Abidjan ji eau   k kaolin kitabu livre   l lame lolo étoile   m main maro riz   n nuage nɔnɔ lait   ɲ oignon ɲɔ mil   ŋ parking ŋɔni épine   o mot bolo bras   oo  looru cinq   on don bon maison   ɔ sort sɔrɔ trouver   ɔɔ  fɔɔnɔ vomir   ɔn  dɔn danser   p pont pan sauter   r  bɔrɔ sac   s sauce sara payer   t tête toto rat   u loup kura nouveau   uu football suuri baisser   un  kunkolo tête   v vol Vamara nom masculin   w doigt wari argent   y papaye yaala se promener   z gaz zɔnzɔn crevette    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mɔgɔ be yen mɔgɔ kɛ mɔgɔ ye</title>
      <link>/2018/05/26/mogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 20:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2018/05/26/mogo/</guid>
      <description>   Mɔgɔ be yen mɔgɔ kɛ mɔgɔ ye.     C&amp;rsquo;est l&amp;rsquo;homme qui fait l&amp;rsquo;homme.   Comme le fer aiguise le fer, ainsi un homme aide son ami à progresser -Prov 27:17 TMN   As iron Sharpens iron, So one man sharpens his friend. -Prov 27:17 NWT    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anki Update</title>
      <link>/2018/05/25/anki/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 13:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2018/05/25/anki/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Its been a while since I have updated my Jula.apkg file for public download. I do realize that flash cards to learn Jula are not the hottest thing right now, but it is a bit of a shame that the &lt;a href=&#34;ankiweb.net people&#34;&gt;[ankiweb.net]&lt;/a&gt; will delete so-called less popular downloads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Datally</title>
      <link>/2018/05/22/datally/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 15:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2018/05/22/datally/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-mobile-data-saving-wifi-app-by-google&#34;&gt;New mobile data-saving &amp;amp; WiFi app by Google&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google has released a new application Datally which enables the user to follow and control apps that chew up bandwith.  Application is free and contains no publicity.  A necessity for those with only 3G/4G connections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jula Alphabet</title>
      <link>/2018/05/22/alphabet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 12:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2018/05/22/alphabet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;jula-alphabet&#34;&gt;Jula Alphabet&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet Still Again ?</title>
      <link>/2018/05/21/ysa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 22:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2018/05/21/ysa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quelle est la différence entre ces trois termes ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Souvent le français est plus précis que l&amp;rsquo;anglais&amp;hellip; surtout en matière de verbes.  Par contre l&amp;rsquo;anglais peut aussi être plus précis que le français.  Voici un exemple:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boyd Kelly on Linkedin</title>
      <link>/2018/05/05/linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 20:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2018/05/05/linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Contact me via linkedin or the contact form below</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just do it!</title>
      <link>/2016/04/21/justdoit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 02:50:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2016/04/21/justdoit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Le slogan publicitaire de Nike n&amp;rsquo;est pas façile à traduire en français. Que veut dire cette expression? Le mot &amp;lsquo;just&amp;rsquo; est un faux ami. Quant il est utilisé comme adjectif, il peut souvent se traduire par &amp;lsquo;juste&amp;rsquo; en voulant dire équitable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/2014/04/02/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2014/04/02/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/2014/04/02/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>bkelly@coastsystems.net (Boyd Kelly)</author>
      <guid>/2014/04/02/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>